<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://kushalarya.com/blog</id>
    <title>Kushal Arya, Full-stack Cloud Developer Blog</title>
    <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://kushalarya.com/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Kushal Arya, Full-stack Cloud Developer Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://kushalarya.com/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>Copyright © 2023 Kushal Arya</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, world.]]></title>
        <id>https://kushalarya.com/blog/hello-world</id>
        <link href="https://kushalarya.com/blog/hello-world"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to social media, I'm definitely more a reader than a writer type of person. Recently I've felt a need to start creating content. Or, more like get back into doing it.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to social media, I'm definitely more a reader than a writer type of person. Recently I've felt a need to start creating content. Or, more like get back into doing it.</p><p>The last time I had a blog was more than 15 years ago. As a teenager, I used to run the "My IT News" WordPress site with, as you may expect, news around IT - especially the new consumer electronics products. While it didn't have much attention (as far as I remember, around ~5k unique visitors per month), I enjoyed doing it. But I had plenty of time and energy back then. Today I'm struggling with both, so... I'm starting a new blog! That makes sense, right?</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="why-yet-another-blog">Why yet another blog<a href="#why-yet-another-blog" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Why yet another blog" title="Direct link to Why yet another blog">​</a></h3><p>Nowadays, everyone has their own blog. Do I really need to become another wannabe influencer?</p><p>No. What I want to achieve is:</p><ul><li>structure my knowledge and record what I've learned recently,</li><li>try out new ways to increase productivity, stay motivated and avoid burnout,</li><li>improve my English (as a non-native English speaker),</li><li>develop self-discipline, reduce procrastination, and, as a result, save time to do the things mentioned above.</li></ul><p>So, as you can see, it's mostly for me, but I hope you'll benefit from this as well.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="what-to-expect">What to expect<a href="#what-to-expect" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to What to expect" title="Direct link to What to expect">​</a></h3><p>Well, definitely shorter, more concise blog posts, like this one.</p><center><p><img loading="lazy" alt="Ain&amp;#39;t nobody got time for that" src="/assets/images/aint-nobody-got-time-for-that-46173cde8ae04c41d9e0674258d080dd.gif" width="220" height="220" class="img_ev3q"> <br><small>source: <a href="https://tenor.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">tenor.com</a></small></p></center><p>While I have a few ideas for new blog posts in mind, I don't want to limit myself to just technical topics. Instead, I will probably touch on different areas of my interest, such as:</p><ul><li>full-stack technical topics related to the technologies I use (Go, Kubernetes, React.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, GraphQL, gRPC...),</li><li>personal projects announcements,</li><li>new talks announcements</li><li>open source,</li><li>cool projects and apps I stumbled upon,</li><li>productivity,</li><li>personal growth (i.e. soft skills),</li><li>finance.</li></ul><p>Yup, that's a lot - but we'll see how it goes.</p><p>At some point, I would also like to experiment with the form of the content. Videos, podcasts? Maybe one day...</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Kushal Arya</name>
            <uri>https://kushalarya.com</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="shorts" term="shorts"/>
        <category label="hello" term="hello"/>
        <category label="world" term="world"/>
        <category label="introduction" term="introduction"/>
    </entry>
</feed>